You brought your tray and silver plate. You
thought you'd open up the gate. You showed me
powder on a glass. You thought you had a man of
class. It was just, it was just a lie. So I wiped it
clean and I watched you die. You called it art.
You called it style. It was just garbage in a
filthy pile.
You held your clipboard like a gun You thought
the battle was already won You crossed the line,
you showed your hand You'll never ever
understand It was just, it was just a lie So I
wiped it clean and I watched you die You called it
art, you called it style It was just garbage in a
filthy pile
It was just, it was just a lot, so I was clean and I
was to die. You call it art, cause you're a fake.
It was just garbage. Make more mistakes!